

Cynthia Fan Front-end developer

I'm a creative and enthusiastic frontend developer with 2+ years of experience building and maintaining responsive websites/applications. I have strong experience with aesthetics and interaction, as well as commitment to the best experience for all users. Diverse professional education experiences have enabled me to understand a variety of user viewpoints.

INFORMATION

Taipei, Taiwan

M +886 936632020

cynthiafan1230@gmail.com Е

EDUCATION

Fu Jen University, Taipei, Taiwan BA in Chinese Literature, 9/2010 - 6/2014

- Minored in Restaurant, Hotel and Institutional Management
- President of student association
- Departmental volleyball team

Korea University, Seoul, South Korea Korean Language Center, 9/2014 - 2/2015

 Passed Test of Proficiency in level 3 Korean (conversational)

LANGUAGES

Mandarin



English

★★☆☆☆

Korean ★★☆☆☆

Native

Intermediate

Conversational

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-end developer | RE

 Participated in brainstorming of products, discussed UI/UX design with other front-end developers and visual designers, worked to achieve improved user experiences and program structure.

- Processed data into graphics such as line charts, pie charts, bar charts, and heat maps via D3.js.
- Developed and maintained several common-use components such as number keyboards and date range selectors.
- Solved problems related to cross-system/device/browser.
- Primary projects:

Official Website

Developed webview pages used in applications, including monthly events, card-fliping games, and questionnaires.

Nuxt Vuex jQuery Typescript Pug SCSS RWD i18n

Store Platform

Maintained and optimized vision and functions, developed new features including shopping cart and member analysis.

Vue Vuex D3 SCSS RWD i18n Express

- CMS

Built from zero a CMS system for the above projects.

Vue Vuex Vue Cli 3 Element UI Pug SCSS

E-currency Member Platform

Built from zero features like KYC, token sale trial and transaction history.

Vue Vuex Vue Cli 3 Element UI Pug SCSS RWD Express

Front-end developer | Crowdinsight

11/2017 - 2/2018

1/2018 - 11/2019

- Initiated and established coding style guide with other front-end developers.
- Primary projects:

Digital Agriculture Platform

Developed website that tracks global farm produce information and processes data into charts, implemented Vuex into project, replaced vue-resource with Axios, and improved development efficiency.

Vue Vuex SCSS

ERP System for Chain Retails

Developed system that provides branch sales statements for managers.

Vue Vuex SCSS Bootstrap

Marketing Manager Lovemove

4/2016 - 1/2017

- Formulated the marketing plan of social media pages and implemented them with colleagues.
- Summarized customized marketing plan for business customers.
- Managed and trained 10 interns to analyze social media page data.

SIDE PROJECTS

Line Bot

Users send keywords to Line Bot to acquire travel information or schedules in lieu of traditional browser search.

Express mLab Heroku

FreeCell Game

Produced as part of Hex School front-end challenges, built with HTML5 drag & drop API.

Vue Heroku

Tech Blog

(In process)

Focus on languages, process of solving bugs, and developing features.

Vuepress

SKILLS

Front-end

Basic

HTML5/Pug CSS3/SCSS

Framework

JavaScript ES6

Vue Nuxt

Library

jQuery D3

Back-end

Language

Node/Express

Database

Mongo/Mongoose

Others

Operating Systems

Mac0S

Version Control System

Git/Git flow

Cloud Service

Heroku AWS EC2

Design Tools

AdobeXD Sketch